Guide to the 11th Street bridges reconstruction project opposition lawsuit records, 2003-2009 MS2356
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
11th Street bridges reconstruction project opposition lawsuit records
2003-2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Herman, Christopher
MS2356
3 Linear Feet
This collection contains documents mostly government documents collected and used as part of a lawsuit to stop the 11th Street bridges project. These records date from 2003-2009.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains primarily government documents collecting and used in a lawsuit to stop the 11th Street bridges project. Most of these records are the environmental impact statements produced as part of the government's work and testimony at government hearings related to this project. These records date from 2003-2009.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical / Historical
These records concern several community groups as they fought to stop the 11th Street bridges project. The bridges plan called for reconstructing a series of bridges that cross the Anacostia River and reconfiguring the interchange of the Southest/Southwest Freeway and the Anacostia Freeway in Southeast DC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Christopher Herman 2016 May 6 (2016.067)
Arrangement
Folders arranged in original order of donation.
Barney Circle (Washington, D.C.); Transportation -- Washington Metropolitan Area; Herman, Christopher
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Statement (FEIS) [1/2], Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Statement (FEIS) [2/2], Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Survey (FEIS) Responses, 26 July 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 11th Street Draft Environmental Impact Statement (DEIS), Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 11th Street Outreach, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 11th Street BR, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 11th Street Finance [1/4], 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 11th Street Finance [2/4], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 11th Street Finance [3/4], 2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 11th Street Finance [4/4], 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 11th Street Early [1/7], 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 11th Street Early [2/7], 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 11th Street Early [3/7], Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 11th Street Early [4/7], 2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 11th Street Early [5/7], 2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 11th Street Early [6/7], 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 11th Street Early [7/7], Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Survey (FEIS) [1/4], 2007 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Survey (FEIS) [2/4], 2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Survey (FEIS) [3/4], 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 11th Street Final Environmental Impact Survey (FEIS) [4/4], Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 11th Street Other Community [1/3], Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 11th Street Other Community [2/3], 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 11th Street Other Community [3/3], 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 11th Street Originals [1/2], 2009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 11th Street Originals [2/2], 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 11th Street CCSIA [1/5], 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 11th Street CCSIA [2/5], 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 11th Street CCSIA [3/5], 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 11th Street CCSIA [4/5], Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 11th Street CCSIA [5/5], 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Middle Anacostia River Crossings Transportation Study Draft, 4 November 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Middle Anacostia River Crossings Transportation Study, June 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)